Oh, you who trick the soul with hopes that fade,
this world is but a shadow and a shade.
You weep for life, yet deep inside you know,
the only peace is found in letting go.
The days are travelers that will not stay.
And happiness is walking a different way.
There is no home awaiting after death,
except the one you built with living breath.
If built with good, a palace you shall find.
If built with sin, you leave all hope behind.
So work for the home where angels guard the gate.
Where the prophet is the neighbor and the rewards are great.
The walls are made of gold, the mortar smells of musk.
A life that never fades into the dusk.
Where are the kings, where is their royal throne?
Where is the glory that the past has known?
How many cities rose beneath the skies,
only to crumble, wither and die?
The cupbearer of death came to their halt,
and poured the wine that ends it for us all.
And now the sands have covered every storm.
The high and low are buried and alone.
Do not trust time, the seconds cut like knives.
A single blink can swallow up our lives.
True nobility is not in gold or birth,
but in the faith you carry on this earth.
Generosity comes first, patience is the key.
A single prayer can set the spirit free.
So work for the home where angels guard the gate.
Where the prophet is the neighbor and the rewards are great.
Its rivers flow with honey and with wine,
for those who seek the mercy of the divine.
This is the garden, eternal and green.
The greatest sight the eyes have ever seen.
And yet my soul will struggle to the end.
I only find the path when I refuse to be my passion's friend.